allfreekidscrafts.com 2019-06-08

# Privacy Policy | AllFreeKidsCrafts.com

**Privacy Policy / Your California Privacy Rights**  
Revised and posted as of March 20, 2018

Prime Publishing, LLC ("Company," "we" or "us") reserves the right to revise this Privacy Policy at any time simply by posting such revision, so we encourage you to review it periodically. In order to track any changes to this Privacy Policy, we will include a historical reference at the top of this document.

**This Privacy Policy will tell you, among other things:**

Your California privacy rights.  
How we collect information and what information we collect.  
How we may use information.  
How we may share information.  
Your choices regarding the sharing of information.

**ACKNOWLEDGEMENT/YOUR AGREEMENT**  
Company websites are not intended for use by individuals under the age of 18. By using our website or submitting information to us, you consent to the Company's use and sharing of the information collected or submitted as described in this Privacy Policy. If you are not 18 years of age or older or you do not agree with the terms of this Privacy Policy, do NOT provide us with any information or use any of the products or services offered or provided on Company websites or through Company technology.

**YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS**  
Beginning January 1, 2005 under California's "Shine the Light" law, California residents who provide personal information in obtaining products or services for personal, family or household use are entitled to either: (1) a list detailing the categories of information shared and the entities to which such information was provided; or (2) to be notified of a mechanism by which a consumer may opt-out of having their information shared with third parties. We have elected the second option. To opt-out of having your information shared with third parties please write to us.

**HOW DO WE COLLECT INFORMATION AND WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?**  
We collect and combine personally identifiable information ("PII") and non-personally identifiable information ("Non-PII") through various sources, including those discussed below. For your reference, PII is data collected with an intention to specifically identify, contact or locate a person, including but not limited to name, address, telephone number, or e-mail address. Conversely, Non-PII is data that is not used to specifically identify, contact or locate an individual, including but not limited to zip code, gender, age, or IP address.

**Distribution Partners**  
Website operators that license our ad serving technology pass information to us so that we may serve advertisements to you. The information passed may include, but is not limited to, your IP address, e-mail address, name, mailing address, telephone number, date of birth, and gender.

**Offer Forms**  
We also collect information about you when you complete a survey or offer form on one of our websites or web pages. This information may include, but is not limited to: your e-mail address, name, mailing address, telephone number, date of birth, gender, and payment information; information about your background, interests, health, education, career goals, and shopping preferences; and any other personal information or unique preference information you provide to us or our advertisers.

**Website Registration Forms**  
We collect information about you when you register on one of our websites. This registration information may include, but is not limited to your:  
e-mail address  
full name  
mailing address  
telephone number  
date of birth  
gender

**Publisher Partners**  
When you complete a registration or offer form that is hosted by one of our website publisher partners on our behalf, the website publisher partner may submit all or a portion of the information that you submitted on the form to the Company. This information may include, but is not limited to: your IP address, e-mail address, name, mailing address, telephone number, date of birth, gender, and payment information; information about your background, interests, health, education, career goals, and shopping preferences; and any other information you provide to our website publisher partner.

**Marketing Partners**  
We may receive information about you, including but not limited to your IP address, e-mail address, first name, last name, mailing address, and telephone number, from third party marketing partners that provide us with consumer data to manage on their behalf.

**Automatic Information/Digital Identifiers**  
We may automatically receive and store certain types of information about you through the data sources listed above.

You may be familiar with the term "cookies," which are unique alphanumeric identifiers that store information on your computer. A cookie is placed on your computer when your web browser accesses our website. We use cookies for tracking transactions and the user characteristics explained in detail throughout this Privacy Policy. If you choose, there are utilities available for purchase from independent software providers to install on your computer as well as tools/preferences you can choose through most web browsers to make website visits anonymous. Of course, cookies let you have a more satisfying website experience, so we recommend that you leave them turned on.

We also collect information through our web server applications. This information includes your Internet Protocol or "IP" address, date/time stamp, browser type, and referring URL.

Additionally, we may use pixel tracking technology to track the completion of transactions with us or our advertisers, the source information for those transactions, and your IP address, date/time stamp, browser type, and referring URL.

**Government Forms**  
The Company may be required to create, collect, maintain, and submit certain information required by the government, such as IRS Forms W-9 and 1099. This information, which may include your taxpayer identification number, will not be used, shared, transferred, or sold for marketing purposes.

**HOW DO WE USE THIS INFORMATION?**  
We may use the collected PII and Non-PII for any legally permissible purpose in our sole discretion, including but not limited to those explained below.

**Ad Serving**  
We may serve advertisements to you based, in part, on your IP address, the demographic and geographic information you submitted to the Company during the website registration process, and other socio-economic information, psychographic information, Internet behavior (i.e., browsing, search, shopping, purchase, and ad response behavior), and lifestyle information about you that we obtain from affiliated entities and from third parties.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads and collect information when users visit our site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements on our site, other websites and other forms of media about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, check out <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.

Company allows firms including [Google](http://www.google.com/), [LiveRamp](http://www.liveramp.com/), [Datonics](http://www.datonics.com/), and [Magnetic](http://www.magnetic.com/) to monitor Company web sites and newsletters for the purpose of reporting website traffic, statistics, advertisements, “click-throughs” and/or other activities. These firms may use cookies, web beacons and other monitoring technologies to compile anonymous statistics about Company users.  Users may go to each firm’s site/URL for information on what is being tracked. Users may go to each firm’s site for information on how to opt-in or opt-out of use of their information and may go to <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp> to opt-out of most third-party tracking.

**EU Residents Important Notice**  
By using our website you consent to us sharing a hashed, non-human readable version of your email with our partners who will drop a cookie on your browser and match your email with its marketing file to create a link between your browser and our partner’s record of you; this link shall be shared by our partner globally for the purpose of improving the relevance of online advertising and content by third parties that are unaffiliated with our website. Our partners use this information to recognize you across different channels and platforms over time for advertising, analytics, attribution, and reporting purposes. Please [click here](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/uk/) to opt out of your data being used for these purposes. This link will direct you to our partner's opt-out centre.

We partner with third parties that collect information across various channels, including offline and online, for purposes of delivering more relevant advertising and content to you. Our partner may place or recognize a cookie on your computer or device and we may share personal information with them if you have submitted such information to us, such as your email address. Our partners may link the personal information we share with them to the cookie stored on your browser or device, and they may collect information such as your IP address, browser or operating system type and version, and demographic or inferred-interest information. Our partners use this information to recognize you across different channels and platforms over time for advertising, analytics, attribution, and reporting purposes. For example, our partners may deliver and/or enable downstream delivery of an ad to you in your web browser based on a purchase you made in a physical retail store, or they may send a personalized marketing email to you based on the fact that you visited a particular website. To learn more about interest-based advertising in general and to opt-out, please visit [https://www.youronlinechoices.com](https://www.youronlinechoices.com/) You can also refuse cookies via the settings of your browser as follow:

For Internet Explorer, [click here](https://support.microsoft.com/en-us/help/278835/how-to-delete-cookie-files-in-internet-explorer)  
For Mozilla Firefox, [click here](https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/enable-and-disable-cookies-website-preferences)  
For Google Chrome, [click here](https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?hl=en&co=GENIE.Platform=Desktop)  
For Safari, [click here](https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT201265)

To know more about Acxiom/Liveramp advertising cookies and opting out:  
US: <https://liveramp.com/opt_out/>  
UK: <http://liveramp.uk/cookies-101/>  
FR: <http://www.acxiom.fr/a-propos-d-acxiom/information-sur-le-depot-de-cookie/>

**Pre-select/Pre-fill Offers**  
Our website technology may pre-select certain offers for you to view based on the demographic and geographic information you submitted to the Company during the website registration process. Additionally, this technology may pre-fill some or all of the offers' data fields with the information you submitted during the website registration process in order to prevent you from having to re-enter this information. We may not show all of the pre-filled data fields to you.

**Upsell**  
We utilize customized post transactional or "upsell" technology to help advertisers generate sales, while providing you with a series of great offers we think may be of interest to you. The way it works is simple: once you purchase a product or service from one of our reward advertisers, you will be offered additional products or services that we think may be of interest to you. If you elect to purchase products or services from an advertiser in the post transactional channel, we will pass the information that you provided during the initial transaction to the subsequent advertiser, including but not limited to your credit card information. This information pass is done to enhance and simplify your purchasing experience. Your information will only be passed to an advertiser in the post transactional channel after you have elected to purchase their product or service. By electing to purchase their product or service you consent to the passing of your data to the third party advertiser in question.

 **Customer Service and Fulfillment**  
We may use your information to operate the website promotion, service your account and to fulfill rewards earned through Company websites. We may also use your information to verify your identity or claimed account status and, where we consider appropriate, investigate your compliance with the terms and conditions of the website promotion or any advertiser offer. We do retain customer service correspondence.

**Credit Card Preauthorization**  
By submitting your credit card information to us or to one of our advertisers, you are authorizing the Company or its agent to periodically verify that your credit card account is valid and has credit available by charging, and thereafter crediting, a small sum to the card.

**Marketing**  
We may use your information in our online (e.g., e-mail marketing) and offline (e.g., telemarketing, cell phone text messaging, skip tracing, and direct mail) marketing programs. If you would like to be removed from these programs please write to us.

**HOW DO WE SHARE INFORMATION?**  
We may share the collected PII and Non-PII for any legally permissible purpose in our sole discretion, including but not limited to those explained below.

**Within the Company**  
We may share information we collect with affiliated companies, including our parent company and other subsidiaries of our parent company, for use in their ad serving and marketing programs. This Privacy Policy does not apply to affiliated companies and their collection, use and sharing of information.

**Vendors**  
We may share your information with various third party vendors that are not part of the Company, including but not limited to vendors that provide us with technology to deploy commercial e-mail, vendors that sell the products or services for which you have qualified through one of our websites, and shipping companies that we utilize to ship products to you.

**Advertisers**  
When you participate in an offer by completing a form, we will transfer the information you submitted on the form to the applicable advertiser.

When you answer "yes" or "no" to a marketing or survey question, some or all of the information that you submitted during the website registration process will be transferred to advertisers that we believe may be of interest to you without providing you with another opportunity to review the information.

When you select "yes" next to an offer, we will transfer some or all of the information that you submitted during the website registration process to the applicable advertiser without providing you with another opportunity to review the information.

**Ad Serving Companies**  
We may use third party ad networks or ad serving companies to serve advertisements on our websites. We pass information about you to these companies so that they can deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of interest to you. The information passed to these companies may include, but is not limited to, your IP address, e-mail address, name, mailing address, telephone number, date of birth, gender, and any other information you provide to us. Web pages that are served by these companies will state that they are "powered by" or "ads by" the applicable company and will contain a link to that company's privacy policy.

  * Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to your website or other websites.
  * Google's use of advertising cookies enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of personalized advertising by visiting [Ads Settings](https://www.google.com/settings/ads). Alternatively, you can opt out of a third-party vendor's use of cookies for personalized advertising by visiting [www.aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/). See below for Canada and EU options.

**Marketing Partners**  
We may share, license or sell your information to third parties for various marketing purposes, including their online (e.g., e-mail marketing) and offline (e.g., telemarketing, cell phone text messaging, skip tracing, and direct mail) marketing programs. If you would like to be removed from these programs write to us.

**Third Party Cookies**  
Notwithstanding anything else in this policy, we or a data provider we have engaged may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser to enable you to receive customized ads or content.   These cookies contain no personally identifiable information.  The cookies may reflect demographic or other data linked to data you voluntarily have submitted to us, e.g., your email address, that we may share with a data provider solely in hashed, non-human readable form.  Our partners use this information to recognize you across different channels and platforms over time for advertising, analytics, attribution, and reporting purposes. Please [click here](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/uk/) to opt out of your data being used for these purposes. This link will direct you to our partner's opt-out center.

**How You Can Control Third Party Advertising Cookies**  
You can use [Ads Settings](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/?hl=en) to manage the Google ads you see and opt out of interest-based ads. Even if you opt out of interest-based ads, you may still see ads based on factors such as your general location derived from your IP address, your browser type and recent, previous searches related to your current search.

In the USA you can opt out of a third-party vendor's use of cookies for personalized advertising at [www.aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/), in Canada at <http://youradchoices.ca/choices>, or the EU-based [Your Online Choices](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/uk/your-ad-choices).

**Data Enhancement/Appending/Validation**  
We may use third party service providers to enhance our database with additional elements, including but not limited to age ranges present in your household, whether you own or rent a home, the length of time you have lived at your residence, whether you are a mail order buyer or responder, household income, and gender. Further, we may use third party service providers to append telephone numbers to other data points we have in our database. We also may use third party service providers to validate the data we have in our database.

Additionally, we may share, license or sell your information to third parties for use in their data validation, enhancement, information verification services, and, to the extent permitted by law, individual reference or look-up services.

**Governmental Agencies or Other Companies**

We may share your information with law enforcement officials or governmental agencies: (1) in response to their request; (2) when permitted or required by law; or (3) to establish our compliance with applicable laws, rules, regulations, or guidelines.

We may store and share your information with third parties for suppression or opt-out purposes.

We also may share your information with third parties when: (1) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions; (2) investigating fraud that has already taken place; (3) enforcing or applying existing terms and conditions and/or other agreements; (4) protecting the rights, property or safety of our websites, our users or others; or (5) responding to subpoenas, court orders or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.

In all cases, this information is not provided to these entities or persons for marketing purposes.

**Right to Transfer**  
Should the Company choose to sell or transfer business assets, it is possible that the information we possess may be transferred as part of that transaction. The Company may decide to retain a copy of the information post sale or transfer.

**COMPANY CUSTOMER CHOICES**

**Marketing Communications and Unsubscribe Information**  
By completing and submitting a Company registration form, you are consenting to receive marketing communications from the Company and its third party marketing partners. If, after you have shared your information with the Company, you decide that you do not want to receive marketing communications or newsletters from the Company and its third party marketing partners, you can discontinue the communications by [clicking here](http://www.favecrafts.com/section/subctr) and filling out our form. If you have registered or submitted information under more than one e-mail account, you must submit separate unsubscribe requests for each account.

**Request for More Information**  
As it relates to marketing communications or any other questions you might have about our Privacy Policy, please write to us at Prime Publishing, LLC, 3400 Dundee Road, Suite 220, Northbrook, IL 60062.

**WHAT HAPPENS IF I HIT A LINK TO ANOTHER SITE FROM A COMPANY WEBSITE?**  
Our websites may offer links to other websites. Other websites have their own terms of use and privacy and security policies. If you choose to visit one of these sites, you should review the policies that govern that particular site.

**APPLICATION OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY**  
This Privacy Policy applies to all information collected by or submitted to the Company. Other affiliated entities of the Company may obtain information independently from transactions and experiences with you or from other sources. This Privacy Policy does not pertain to that information.

**WHAT IS THE POLICY WITH RESPECT TO COMMUNICATING WITH CHILDREN?**  
We recognize the unique privacy concerns regarding children. We are committed to carefully protecting privacy where children are involved no matter the point of contact. In particular, our intention is to fully comply with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act ("COPPA"). Per COPPA guidelines, we do not knowingly collect PII from children under the age of 13. If a parent or guardian is made aware that a child under the age of 13 has provided us with PII through any point of contact, click here to contact us and we will delete the information about the child referenced from our files.

**SECURITY**  
There is no such thing as complete security on the Internet or otherwise. The Company uses various security techniques on our websites to help protect against the loss, misuse or modification of information we've collected from you. When you access your personal information or transmit information to us, that information is stored on servers that we have taken steps to protect from unauthorized access or intrusion. While we strive to protect your information, the Company cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us. You acknowledge and assume this risk when communicating with the Company, its partners and affiliates.

**LIMITATION OF LIABILITY**  
YOU UNDERSTAND AND AGREE THAT ANY DISPUTE OVER PRIVACY IS SUBJECT TO THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY, AS WELL AS THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THIS WEBSITE (INCLUDING LIMITATIONS ON DAMAGES). YOU AGREE THAT THE COMPANY'S LIABILITY FOR ANY BREACH OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY SHALL BE LIMITED TO THE VALUE OF THE TRANSACTIONS OR SERVICES PROVIDED TO YOU BY THE COMPANY TO THE EXTENT SUCH CLAIM IS NOT OTHERWISE BARRED BY OUR TERMS AND CONDITIONS.
